‎I'm goin' home early! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
‎SEASONAL SPRING VEG SALE
‎GREAT VALUE - PICKED TODAY
‎Next, please.
‎Okay.
‎20% OFF - HALF PRICE
‎ALCOHOL - RICE CRACKERS
‎That'll be 1, 040 yen.
‎Okay.
‎Here is your change.
‎-You should have enough points soon.
‎-Okay.
‎You'll get a coupon
‎for 50% off rice crackers tomorrow.
‎Thanks.
‎Yamada. Time to swap out.
‎Something's up.
‎TYPICALLY
‎Wow, so many points!
‎Thank you very much.
‎My customer service
‎fell short of raising spirits.
‎Did it?
‎I need a cigarette.
‎I hope I'll see you again, Sasaki.
‎Tayama--
‎I probably shouldn't smoke here
‎just 'cause it'll be easy for me to do so.
‎Hello. I'm an easy woman.
‎Tayama?
‎'Sup?
‎-Did you just finish your shift?
‎-Yep.
‎Good work today.
‎More to the point,
‎you came for a smoke, right?
‎You came for me, right?
‎Come on in.
‎Okay. Please excuse my intrusion.
‎That's an awfully big sigh.
‎Had a bad day, Sasaki?
‎Well, I guess so.
‎Yamada's worried about you.
‎I wonder, was I unpleasant toward her?
‎You weren't.
‎She just thought you seemed down, and
‎she's worried about whether you're okay.
‎That Yamada really is
‎a wonderful and attentive store clerk.
‎And thank you too, Tayama.
‎I'm just the messenger.
‎But didn't you go out of your way
‎to come and tell me this?
‎And your hair is down.
‎Maybe you couldn't wait
‎to get here and tell me--
‎Tayama!
‎You shouldn't blow smoke
‎in people's faces!
‎My hair's this way
‎because I was feeling lazy.
‎And as for why I wanted to tell you...
‎I'm not gonna say.
‎Because you're being cheeky today.
‎Cheeky? What?
‎How am I being cheeky?
‎You're very cheeky for someone so dense.
‎No! I'm not dense!
‎Maybe I am dense.
‎What happened?
‎Well, Tayama...
‎I'd appreciate
‎your objective feedback here.
‎Shoot.
‎Am I actually scary?
‎Are you all right?
‎Why are you asking
‎such a strange question?
‎Is it strange?
‎Well, you see...
‎I made the new grad cry today.
‎Wait, what? Are you the type
‎to fly off the handle at work?
‎That is so funny.
‎Why, you... Why, you!
‎No! I do not!
‎It was such a minor mistake,
‎so I was trying to cheer her up.
‎But I must have come across
‎as the complete opposite.
‎KEEP THINGS TIDY AND IN ORDER
‎Better luck next time.
‎Wait.
‎What the hell did you do, Sasaki?
‎I'm very sorry.
‎Poor Sasaki really got chewed out, hey?
‎I hear he made the new grad cry.
‎What? Our Sasaki?
‎I'd hate to think she hates
‎her job now because of me.
‎So what if she does?
‎Your job involves
‎tolerating a shitty toxic workplace
‎that makes you work
‎late into the night, right?
‎She's gonna leave no matter what.
‎Oh, Tayama.
‎And if she's a new grad, that means
‎she's only just joined the company, yeah?
‎She'll figure it out soon enough.
‎She'll know that you're a good egg.
‎Well, that is if she doesn't quit first.
‎Thank you.
‎I'll bet this sort of thing
‎never happens to Yamada.
‎Why Yamada, of all people?
‎Well, I was just thinking
‎I'll bet Yamada wouldn't scare a new grad,
‎nor would she make them cry.
‎You mean unlike me, who must
‎scare people off based off looks alone.
‎No, I didn't mean it like that.
‎True, Yamada may be the type
‎who gets looked down upon,
‎but she's definitely not the scary type.
‎Looked down upon?
‎I think she's amazing.
‎She works late into the night,
‎and she does it with a smile,
‎and she even worries herself
‎over customers like me.
‎I wish I could plug away with a smile
‎the way Yamada does.
‎It's 'cause the supermarket
‎is always making us practice our smiles.
‎Really?
‎Even you?
‎Yeah.
‎"Squint to make little crescent-moon eyes.
‎Flex your facial muscles.
‎Show your upper teeth."
‎Like this!
‎Tayama... You...
‎Sorry. I'm so sorry.
‎I mean, you kind of scared me there.
‎What a lovely,
‎sweet smile you have, Tayama.
‎Tayama?
‎Now it's my turn to say sorry, Sasaki.
‎You see, it's faster to do it this way
‎than with just a demonstration.
‎Sorry, Tayama. Are you mad?
‎I really didn't mean it.
‎All right. Smile Practice is over.
‎Sorry, Tayama.
‎Remember what I taught you,
‎and make me proud.
‎-But I--
‎-Got it?
‎Yes, ma'am!
‎HAPPY CORP.
‎I am very sorry about yesterday.
‎I didn't mean to start crying, but...
‎But it all just sort of came out.
‎It's smoky in here,
‎so let's take this outside.
‎No, it's fine.
‎I'm very sorry
‎for making you out to be the bad guy.
‎No, I should have been
‎more careful with my words.
‎That's not true at all.
‎I know you're a good person, and still I...
‎What?
‎She'll figure it out soon enough.
‎She'll know that you're a good egg.
‎Everyone makes mistakes
‎when they're first starting out.
‎Try not to let it get to you.
‎If you ever need any help,
‎please feel free to reach out.
‎Thank you.
‎LET'S KEEP THIS PLACE
‎NEAT AND TIDY
‎You sweet talker, you.
‎Stop that! Don't ruin it!
‎SUPER S
‎Next, please.
‎Here is your receipt.
‎Thank you.
‎Thank you, and have a nice day.
‎What a lovely,
‎sweet smile you have, Tayama.
‎How dare you laugh, Sasaki?
‎You should be used to it.
‎I came out for smokes with only
‎one layer on because it's spring.
‎But it still gets quite cold out at night.
‎Maybe I'll just have one puff
‎before heading home.
‎Yamada. Time to swap out.
‎'Kay.
‎He didn't stop by today.
‎Is he working overtime?
‎Staying the night? Until morning?
‎Oh, and Yamada...
‎Yes?
‎The store manager wants
‎to speak with you before you leave.
‎Tayama. Good eve--
‎MOODY
‎Oh, my.
‎SOMEBODY'S CRANKY...
‎Well, if it isn't good old Sasaki.
‎Hello.
‎Well, don't just stand there.
‎Come sit with me.
‎Right.
‎-Is everything all right--
‎-Sasaki. Did you have today off?
‎Yes, strangely enough.
‎Just what you'd say
‎when you have a toxic workplace.
‎I'm glad you got the day off.
‎COLD - WARM
‎Not smoking today?
‎It's cold out, so I need a drink.
‎Would you like one too?
‎If you're feeling a little off,
‎don't they always say a warm drink
‎is better than smokes or alcohol?
‎I got a complaint.
‎First one in a long time.
‎"She's always got great customer service,
‎but it's disappointing
‎when she smells like cigarettes."
‎The store manager said it was uncalled for
‎and that I shouldn't worry about it, but...
‎But a complaint like that
‎makes me feel like a complete idiot.
‎What a lonely person.
‎To lose faith in someone
‎you thought was great
‎just because you see a new side to them,
‎even though they're still the same person...
‎But I'm overstepping here.
‎I don't even know which section
‎of the supermarket you work in--
‎Sorry. I didn't wear enough today,
‎and now I can't stop sneezing--
‎Tayama! What are you--
‎You can borrow this.
‎It's warm.
‎Thank you, Tayama.
‎No. Thank you.
‎And I'm sorry, Sasaki.
‎-I can't drink coffee.
‎-What?
‎You look surprised.
‎No, it's not that.
‎I actually can't have it either.
‎Shall I just get a juice instead?
‎I'll have a Depovita.
‎What beautiful weather.
‎I love this spring weather.
‎It seeps straight into my bones.
‎Especially after getting
‎absolutely chewed out by that client.
‎I am so sorry! So very sorry!
‎And now I have to go back to the office.
‎I might get some food
‎from Super S on the way.
‎Tayama must be on the night shift.
‎I doubt she'll be there.
‎Tayama--
‎Yamada?
‎Hello.
‎What are you doing here?
‎Don't tell me you work afternoons as well?
‎It's okay, Sasaki. Calm down.
‎I'm terribly sorry.
‎I'm usually on the night shift,
‎but today I'm on the afternoon one
‎because we're so short-staffed.
‎And as to why I'm here...
‎Calm down.
‎This is the only vending machine we have.
‎I see.
‎Are you off early today?
‎No, I'm just heading back to work,
‎but I thought if Tayama were here,
‎I might join her for a smoke--
‎I'm sorry, Yamada.
‎I know I don't work here, but...
‎It's just that I was taking up
‎Tayama's kind invitation to join her.
‎Please don't fault her for it.
‎And so...
‎It's fine, Sasaki.
‎I already know.
‎Tayama already told me.
‎PON!
‎You really do talk
‎to her about everything.
‎You must be really good friends.
‎Dense-saki.
‎DENSE-SAKI
‎-Come again?
‎-Yes! We are great friends.
‎I thought as much.
‎I'm sure you have a lot in common.
‎Seeing as you both have a real knack
‎when it comes to reading others.
‎Oh, and Yamada...
‎Yes?
‎Well,
‎is Tayama doing okay?
‎Yeah, she's fine.
‎Are you referring
‎to the complaint she received?
‎Yes.
‎Sorry, but Tayama and I
‎were talking about it a little.
‎I was wondering how she was doing.
‎She's fine.
‎I was worried about her too,
‎but she said she had some ramen,
‎went to bed, and forgot all about it.
‎I see. Well, that's good to hear.
‎I hope you'll continue
‎to lend her an ear, Sasaki.
‎Yes, but...
‎Is it really a good idea to rehash
‎something she's already put to bed?
‎It doesn't have to be
‎about this thing in particular.
‎I'll make sure to tell her
‎you were worried about her.
‎COLD
‎Are you sure?
‎I really wouldn't want to overstep.
‎You've already lent an ear.
‎Would it really
‎still be considered overstepping?
‎Well, I guess not.
‎By the way, Yamada,
‎thank you for before.
‎Tayama told me.
‎She said you were worried about me
‎that time I was feeling down.
‎I didn't want to be a bother
‎by standing and chatting at your register,
‎so I never really
‎got the chance to thank you.
‎It was nothing.
‎I'd had a rough day at work,
‎so I was really grateful.
‎It meant a lot to know
‎that someone actually cared.
‎It's fine.
‎But I hope I didn't overstep too much.
‎You thought you were overstepping?
‎Look at that. Now I'm saying it.
‎I guess that's just how it goes, huh?
‎I'm sorry!
‎I'm prattling on and keeping you here.
‎It's fine.
‎I was happy I got to chat with you
‎the same way that Tayama does.
‎Tayama may not be around,
‎but feel free to stay
‎and smoke if you'd like.
‎Thank you.
‎Actually, I think I'll head back
‎without a smoke break today.
‎I'd hate for you to end up
‎stuck with the smell.
‎Sorry to bother you on your break.
‎See you.
‎Sasaki.
‎Yes?
‎You had a flower petal
‎stuck to you this whole time.
‎What? This whole time?
‎You did.
‎Fancy that. A flower petal
‎on some old geezer's head...
‎You looked cute, so I didn't say anything.
‎Sorry about that.
‎No, thank you.
‎Yamada can be a little...
‎mischievous.
‎Sasaki is so dense.
‎It's weird.
‎Subtitle translation by: Rychelle Brittain